



I'm Elias Pinheiro

Software developer

AGE 22

ADDRESS R. Quinta lt 102 Parceiros - Leiria

E-MAIL schmeisk@gmail.com

PHONE +351915896602

I have an open mind and always searching for new ideas to improve each day and I'm an independent person who's able to adapt to new conditions, as I've lived as an Erasmus student in Croatia and Brazil for five months. And I won a program (VIOP) and I went to Finland for fifteen days at the Helsinki University.

I have ability to work under pressure and striving for customer satisfaction as a result of working with sales and being waiter.

I have great interpersonal and communication skills, I've worked with sales, multilevel marketing. I have a passion to do lectures, I already did some presentations about "Living abroad", also for programming and solve problems. That feeling when I solve a big problem is awesome and I would like to have that this feeling all of my life.

Professional Skills

Java	80%	JavaScript	60%
Object Oriented Programming	85%	HTML5	80%
SQL	80%	Agile Methodologies	85%

Work Experience

2015 - 2015

Interact Solutions

Front End Developer

Acquire agile development skills, in this case Scrum. Development of pages to television of the company using mostly JavaScript and sometimes JavaEE.

2014 - 2014

IPI eiria

JAVAEE Developer

Acquire JavaEE skills as I developed an application to manage a pharmacy story, like sales, suppliers, products.

2014 - 2014

IPLeiria

Java developer

Acquire OOP skills as I developed a game in Java called Birzzle.



2012 - 2012

SANO

WEB Developer

I developed an online store in Joomla from scratch.

Education

2015 - 2017

Doing Master of Mobile Computing

IPleiria

2009 - 2012

Computer and Management technician

Escola Secundaria de Ourem

2012 - 2015

Bachelor Computer Engineering

IPLeiria